<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!-- -*- coding: utf-8;-*- -->
<Infoproblemtype version="1.0">
  <Program n="ramdebugger">
    <Name>RamDebugger</Name>
    <Version>7.2</Version>
    <Section>contrib/devel</Section>
    <Categories>Development;Debugger;IDE;Application</Categories>
    <Dependencies>libc6 (&gt;= 2.3.6-6), 
      libx11-6, libxext6</Dependencies>
    <Maintainer>Compass Engineering &lt;info@compassis.com&gt;</Maintainer>
    <Homepage>http://www.compassis.com</Homepage>
    <Languages>
      <Language n="en">English</Language>
    </Languages>
      <ShortDescription>RamDebugger is a graphical debugger for the scripting lenguage Tcl-TK.</ShortDescription>
    <Description>
       Graphical debugger for the scripting language Tcl-TK.
	
	With RamDebugger, it is possible to make Local Debugging, where the debugger starts
	the program to be debugged. and Remote debugging, where the program to debug is already
	started and RamDebugger connects to it.

	FEATURES
	
	* IDE for code edition of TCL, XML and c/c++
	* Full debugging of TCL and c/c++
	* Works in Linux, Windows and MacOSX
	* It supports editing XML code
	* It contains a GUI for version control system (cvs or fossil)
    </Description>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.2" date="2009-10-23"> 
	*  New default font for Linux
	*  Move to view all when view files or variables pane is activated
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.1" date="2009-10-23"> 
	 *  Added text files line end control. It is possible to select auto, Unix or Windows
	 *  When saving, Open previously read files with r+ and truncate to avoid problems with links
	 *  It is possible to debug c/c++ code attaching to a running process
	 * When saving, file is not deleted and recreated, but open an truncated. In this way, symbolic links work ok
	 *  New keyboard accelerator: Alt-Backspace
	 *  Possibility to hide view variables pane
	 *  Instrumentation and coloring of Makefile files
	 *  It is possible to manage files under the version control system fossil
	 * The source version control system has been moved from cvs to fossil
	 * Double click in one #ifdef in c/++ code selects the block
	 * It is possible to define the type of the file with one special line at the beginning of the file, emacs style
	 * New menu command to define the type of the file manually
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.0" date="2009-08-23">
	  * Interative search and replace with Ctrl-i and Ctrl-j
	  * Add some functions for CVS management of the files being edited
	  * Fast instrumentation of c/c++ code
	  * Create a c/c++ project based on an existing Makefile
	  * First version for MacOSX
	  * There is a new option to be added to the debugged program that permits it to wait for the debugger to connect. Check example "example2b.tcl"
	  * There is a new option to decide if saving with Tabs or with spaces at the beginning of the lines of the edited files
    </NewsInVersion>
  </Program>
</Infoproblemtype>
