<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!-- -*- coding: utf-8;-*- -->
<Infoproblemtype version="1.0">
  <Program n="ramdebugger">
    <Name>RamDebugger</Name>
    <Version>7.3</Version>
    <Section>contrib/devel</Section>
    <Categories>Development;Debugger;IDE;Application</Categories>
    <Dependencies>libc6 (&gt;= 2.3.6-6), 
      libx11-6, libxext6</Dependencies>
    <Maintainer>Compass Engineering &lt;info@compassis.com&gt;</Maintainer>
    <Homepage>http://www.compassis.com</Homepage>
    <Languages>
      <Language n="en">English</Language>
    </Languages>
      <ShortDescription>RamDebugger is a graphical debugger for the scripting lenguage Tcl-TK.</ShortDescription>
    <Description>
       Graphical debugger for the scripting language Tcl-TK.
	
	With RamDebugger, it is possible to make Local Debugging, where the debugger starts
	the program to be debugged. and Remote debugging, where the program to debug is already
	started and RamDebugger connects to it.

	FEATURES
	
	* IDE for code edition of TCL, XML and c/c++
	* Full debugging of TCL and c/c++
	* Works in Linux, Windows and MacOSX
	* It supports editing XML code
	* It contains a GUI for version control system (cvs or fossil)
    </Description>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.3" date="2009-11-16"> 
	*  Fixed error with "diff window" in vcs
	*  New capabilities for fossil management: Differences window, insert tickets number, insert file name
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.2" date="2009-10-23"> 
	*  New default font for Linux
	*  Move to view all when view files or variables pane is activated
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.1" date="2009-10-23"> 
	 *  Added text files line end control. It is possible to select auto, Unix or Windows
	 *  When saving, Open previously read files with r+ and truncate to avoid problems with links
	 *  It is possible to debug c/c++ code attaching to a running process
	 *  When saving, file is not deleted and recreated, but open an truncated. In this way, symbolic links work ok
	 *  New keyboard accelerator: Alt-Backspace
	 *  Possibility to hide view variables pane
	 *  Instrumentation and coloring of Makefile files
	 *  It is possible to manage files under the version control system fossil
	 * The source version control system has been moved from cvs to fossil
	 * Double click in one #ifdef in c/++ code selects the block
	 * It is possible to define the type of the file with one special line at the beginning of the file, emacs style
	 * New menu command to define the type of the file manually
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="7.0" date="2009-08-23">
	  * Interative search and replace with Ctrl-i and Ctrl-j
	  * Add some functions for CVS management of the files being edited
	  * Fast instrumentation of c/c++ code
	  * Create a c/c++ project based on an existing Makefile
	  * First version for MacOSX
	  * There is a new option to be added to the debugged program that permits it to wait for the debugger to connect. Check example "example2b.tcl"
	  * There is a new option to decide if saving with Tabs or with spaces at the beginning of the lines of the edited files
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="6.2">
	  *  Prepared for new TCL syntax {*}
	  *  Changes From version 5.6 to version 6.1
	  *  Partly converted to tile
	  *  Prepared for working with TabletPC
	  *  Highly optimized XML parsing and colorize
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="5.6">
	  *  Added trace command in the Breakpoints window (checking in every line if a variable changes)
	  *  New debug option: Continue out of loop
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="5.5">
	  *  Added new option Open in new Window
	  *  Added a new Return option to the debugger for returning from a proc without finishing it
	  *  Edit--Paste stack
	  *  New macro for changing background color to regions of file
	  *  Possibility of non-instrumenting some procs, defined by name
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="5.4">
	  *  Colorize XML files
	  *  New open without browser
	  *  Permmits to open remote files by using ssh, ftp, plink.
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="5.3">
	  *  Colors customization
	  *  Fast instrumenter for TCL code, developed in C++
	  *  Profile procedures
	  *  Files list obtained with Ctrl-Tab has a new alternative list based on current directory
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="4.4">
	  *  Implemented secondary view in the Editor
	  *  Implemented auto save, based on file revisions
	  *  New inline file chooser to fast change buffers
	  *  The search controls are now integrated inside the main GUI
	  *  RamDebugger can automatically manage revisions of files (based internally on CVS)
	  *  Added program  for visualizing file differences
	  *  New option in Help to associate RamDebugger as command in the .tcl extension in Windows
	  *  When TCL raises and error, RamDebugger shows last visited line
	  *  If files contain, in first lines something like  they are considered as in utf-8 encoding
	  *  RamDebugger works only for TCL version 8.4
	  *  Open file and save file browser follow the preferences extensions for file types
	  *  Added new macro for going to function names
	  *  Corrections for when several pop-up windows appear at the same time
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="3.2">
	  *  Added Snit support
	  *  Added contextual menu in marker zone (left margin of text)
	  *  Added Enable/disable to breakpoints
	  *  Added command stop in the Debug menu
	  *  Added command to break execution in any moment
	  *  Added zoom option to Display Windows hierarchy
	  *  The cache directory (used internally by RamDebugger) is now created in the user directories instead of inside the installation directory
	  *  Option Pick window in Windows hierarchy
	  *  It is necessary to stop debugging before start debugging again
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="3.1">
	  *  GiD customization files
	  *  User can choose file extensions for every file type
	  *  New macro for applying regsub to a region
	  *  New option in Current file arguments: file type can be TCL or TK
	  *  New option in Current file arguments: Another file can be started to begin local debugging
	  *  RamDebugger::OpenFileSaveHandler
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="3.0">
	  *  Count lines of code of a project (LOC)
	  *  It is possible to create and use macros defined in TCL
	  *  Values in User defined var and Local vars display content in balloon
	  *  Autodisplay variables now displays also array variables
	  *  Better interactive indentation and colors
	  *  Menu close
	  *  Drawing dynamically closing braces when editing
	  *  better stack position
	  *  search and replace
	  *  comment lines are indented in normal column
	  *  Added reinstrument to menu Debug
	  *  If tkcon is open, output goes also to tkcon
	  *  New menu options in Tkcon to send commands to debugged program
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="2.8">
	  *  Option to instrument last line in proc (to avoid error when not using return)
	  *  corrected error when brackets are not paired in comments
	  *  Script of command bind is now instrumented
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="2.6">
	  *  RamDebugger can now be used as a package
	  *  When editing one file, breakpoints are modified in position accordingly
	  *  Command console works correctly now in local mode
	  *  It is possible to save possitions in the editor to return later
	  *  Activated drag and drop (works for Windows and for platforms that have package tkdnd compiled).
    </NewsInVersion>
    <NewsInVersion version="2.0">
	  *  Tested for Tcl/Tk 8.4
	  *  When Tkhtml is not compiled for the given platform, gives message and continues
	  *  Added contextual help for programming commands. If there are manual pages (UNIX), it also uses them if man2html is found in the system.
	  *  When debugging local, possibility to choose debug TCL or TK
	  *  Improved the build process and the debugging for C/C++
	  *  Improved several windows, like the Breakpoints window and Goto line
	  *  Added option to search in files
	  *  Several speed problems in linux were related to the TCL bug with raise command. Implemented one workaround.
	  *  Fixed many bugs related to parsing files and other.
    </NewsInVersion>
  </Program>
</Infoproblemtype>
